Human. Nature.
The Legend of Tarzan is a fantasy, action,
adventure film directed by David Yates.
Tarzan, having acclimated to life in London, is called back to his former home in
the jungle to investigate the activities at a mining encampment.
John Clayton / Tarzan, played by Alexander Skarsgård.
Captain Leon Rom, played by Christoph Waltz.
George Washington Williams, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Jane Porter, played by Margot Robbie.
Chief Mbonga, played by Djimon Hounsou.
Prime Minister, played by Jim Broadbent.
The Legend of Tarzan is a 2016 action adventure film directed by David Yates.
Based on the character Tarzan created by Edgar Rice Burroughs, the film
features an ensemble cast including Alexander Skarsgård, Samuel L.
Jackson, Margot Robbie, Djimon Hounsou, and Christoph Waltz.
The story follows John Clayton (Tarzan), who, after moving to London, is convinced by George Washington
Williams to return to his former home in the jungles of Africa, to investigate claims of slavery.
Principal photography began on June 21, 2014, at Leavesden Studios
in the United Kingdom and wrapped four months later.
The film premiered at the Dolby Theatre in Los Angeles on June 29, 2016, and was
theatrically released in the United States on July 1, 2016, by Warner Bros.
It grossed $356.7 million worldwide against a budget of $180
million and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of africa, animal attack, feral child, tarzan, jungle.